Love Me Like MeHave
Me Love MeLove Me Love Miguel
mec,
love me Gotta hate Aloha
Reso, love meambirado Love me, love me I
like you I like you My abundance Hello,
I'm here I love you I like you,
I like you, I like you I love you,
I love you Lage I don't do
something For sure It ain't
I don't do something I
like you I song Baby I just
I song Baby I just My eyes fall
fall in my death, Bumma's wand on,
Yore shimai yo, Sarabama da hai ima Show!
Then there were two,
and then three of them.
And I thought if they take me
in now, my cat's gonna die.
My place doesn't allow pets.
So you see, I'm the only
one who knows about him.
In Morioka City, Iwate
Prefecture, in March of 2016,
two people, a young girl and her mother,
were found fatally
stabbed in their own home.
The Morioka Prosecutor's Office indicted
Code Owe, who lived near the crime scene.
He was charged with
felony murder and robbery.
The events leading to
his arrest were thus.
While being questioned by three officers
on patrol, Code Oe suddenly fled.
The patrolman chased Oe to his home.
Once inside, the officers
discovered a knife covered in blood.
Oe was arrested in flagrante delicto.
After DNA analysis,
the blood on the blade was revealed
to be a match to the victim's DNA.
O .A.
consistently denied all charges Asked
to explain the knife, he insisted.
I just picked it up.
It wasn't mine.
A little hard to believe,
don't you think so?
He didn't flee questioning
because of his cat.
He fled because he was guilty.
I don't think so.
He had been wrongly detained
by the police before.
When an acquaintance of his
was busted for using drugs?
You're saying the police traumatized him?
But even so, I picked it up Who
picks up a bloody knife? No one.
He claims he was planning to
turn it in to the police later.
Later?
I know, I know.
His claims are all hard to believe.
But when you consider Owe's background,
the fact he works as a live-in
employee at a non-profit organization,
it definitely starts
sounding plausible to me.
What kind of non-profit?
A shelter for the elderly
who have nowhere else to go.
They provide support for
their independent living.
Owe's job was taking care of
the residents who lived there.
However, they didn't pay
him a salary with wages.
They only supplied him
with goods, like groceries,
boxed lunches, and gifts of pocket
money for New Year's sometimes.
And if you could believe it,
they still charged him 50,000
yen a month for rent on his room.
Brutal.
Apparently, quite a few of the
residents have prior records.
Anyway, when asked why he didn't turn
in the knife as soon as he found it...
The rules say we can't call cop cars.
or ambulances either they don't want
loud sirens bothering the neighbors
a non-profit sounds pretty suspicious yeah
it's extremely close to
being outright illegal
since the earthquake relief
funds started flowing into this
region we've seen an increase
in suspiciously managed npos
so it's possible the murder
weapon was just lying
there i think there's a
good chance that oa is
innocent.
First, we'll investigate the
organization's activities and tax filings,
then run background checks
on all the residents.
I'll focus on getting more
information out of OA.
You handle the investigation, Shimizu.
You're dumping a huge job
like that on me out of the
blue?
And could you take care
of his cat? His cat?
The commission on a public defender case
is zilch, no matter how many hours we bill.
And the public always
assumes they're guilty.
Plus, there's no suspended
sentence in murder cases,
so he could get the death penalty.
There's nothing to gain
by taking this case.
Higuruma,
will you please explain to me why you
go around accepting cases like this one?
It's good once in a while.
If we stuck to easy work,
our skills would dull.
It's more than once in a while.
It's more than once in a while!
You're saying your
thoughts out loud again.
Sounds like Higuruma
hasn't changed a bit then.
It's tough working for an independent
lawyer who isn't in it for the money.
Yeah, well, at least I'm not stuck having
to run a cafe on the side like you are.
Hey, wait a minute.
When you say he hasn't changed, you
mean Higuruma's always been like this?
Hmm? Not really.
I think he actually
used to be a lot worse.
Huh.
Back when he was with us,
he was in charge of a reckless
driving case that resulted in injury.
Specifically, it was for drunk driving.
The defendant was only 19,
and his co-workers had
coerced him into doing
both the drinking part
and the driving part.
However, those involved
all aligned their stories,
and he didn't have the
money for a settlement,
and we couldn't get him
a suspended sentence.
You liar!
You promised me they
would find me innocent!
You promised to get him a suspended
sentence, not an innocent verdict,
although you didn't manage to
do either, so there's that.
You know what the takeaway from this is?
Quit being a criminal defense
lawyer for impossible cases.
Trying to save the week
may be a noble endeavor,
but there's a limit to
what lawyers like us can do
without any cooperation from
the courts and prosecutors.
They don't want to sit and
hear a client's sob story.
They just want to clear their dockets.
It's not worth continuing
when your clients resent you.
They're at the end of their rope,
both mentally and financially.
I can't blame them for lashing out at me.
But Higuruma, what
about your mental state?
Well, I'm...
We, the people, find
the defendant innocent.
Innocent? What?
He actually won this case?
Not yet.
They'll appeal right away.
The prosecution is appealing.
After the police searched your room for
stolen items, nothing was found there.
And in the same non-profit residence,
another person went missing right
after the crime was committed.
Luckily, you were caught on the
security feet of a convenience store.
That and the condition
of the corpses proved you
couldn't have been at
the scene of the murders.
Boy, it's a good thing you don't
know how to cook for yourself.
Higuruma, sir.
I want to thank you for everything.
There's no need to call me sir.
We're not in the clear yet.
There's still the appeal.
That's not what I mean.
You're the only one who
believed me. Thank you.
While defense lawyers have to work
with limited budgets and manpower,
prosecutors can use taxpayer money to pour
on the lawyers and dig up the evidence.
That's fine.
It's how the system works.
However, the prosecutors didn't submit
any new evidence during the second trial.
trial.
The judge accepted their absurd claim that
there was no reason to
consider the missing
person as a suspect.
So they overturned the verdict.
The highest court is always the
bottleneck for a third trial.
Most final appeals are
turned away at the door.
It's challenging
to even get a proper trial there.
This trial was destined for a
guilty verdict from the start.
Why are you looking at me that way?
But Higuruma, what
about your mental state?
Well, I'm not trying to promote
the ideals of saving the weak.
It's just always gone
against my nature to leave
things alone when I
feel like they're wrong.
I've just never been
able to fix that habit.
The Goddess of Justice blinds her sight
to maintain fairness under the law,
and people turn a blind eye to all
kinds of things to protect themselves.
But I don't want to brush away the hands
of people who cling to me for help.
The least I can do is keep my eyes open.
If there are any objections?
To today's trial!
Submit your final appeal in writing.
Within 15 days.
Which includes today?
Higuruma, what are you doing?
Everyone come back.
We're having a retrial!
Higuruma's in.
Shinjuku. Ikebukuro.
Got it? Shinjuku.
I hope Itadori's headed there too?
Ikebukuro, huh?
I wonder if Fushiguro's there.
Oh, isn't she running a little late
that girl better get here soon or else!
But if she doesn't have my next sucker
with her, she'd better not come at all.
What's your problem no no no
no we asked the questions.
What are you doing around here, huh?
This is getting old
Why are you keeping quiet?
You're better off laughing with us.
Oh dear, what did I tell you?
Not that I actually told you,
but why can't you understand?
Are you an idiot?
These guys aren't that smart or athletic,
but they're brimming with pride.
All you have to do is just match their
attitude and joke around with them,
so you don't hurt that ego of theirs.
Then you won't get targeted
by anyone else either and
you might even have a good
time now and then knock it
off hmm here comes another
idiot is that uniform from
West Middle you're a middle
school you need to learn some
respect.
We're gonna teach you a lesson.
Down you go!
Huh?
You really shouldn't be so violent!
And you?
Y-you mean me?
Hey.
What now?
You aren't planning to go through
Ikebukuro to reach Shinjuku, are you?
That area is rich with supplies.
We're more likely to
encounter other players.
There are two reasons for going this way.
The route is easy to follow, and
I happen to have a base nearby.
I'm just dying to take a shower.
I haven't had a chance
to rest since yesterday.
Higuruma uses this theater as his base.
Assuming he hasn't moved, that is.
Oh, cool.
You've been a big help, man.
Thank you.
Uh, wait a minute. Hold up. Don't go!
What is it?
You're seriously going in?
Well, I'd have preferred to go in
with my friend, but I'm in a hurry.
I never actually met Higuruma myself,
but I once saw him beat Haba
to a pulp right in front of me.
Then I'll totally be okay.
I beat Propeller Head too, which means
I'll at least be able to run away.
See you later.
Tell him.
Come on, man, tell him.
You should stop doing this.
I'm sorry, Hitotori.
It's about time, Higuruma.
Sorry, I guess we were
both expecting to see him.
I'm Reggie.
And she deceived you.
Don't give me that look.
You don't scare me for a second.
And just so you know, Reggie here...
Quiet!
I'm wasting my time here.
Who's there?
What are you doing here?
I could ask you that.
Ever have the chance to take a bath
while still fully clothed? Never.
Surprisingly, it feels better
than I expected it would.
You know, back when I
was in elementary school,
I loved our safety classes
on swimming and clothes.
So many things have stopped
mattering to me lately,
so I've been challenging myself to try
things I assumed I shouldn't be doing.
I've basically gone off the
rails after hitting my mid-30s.
Funny, huh?
I guess it's kind of amusing.
You're Higuruma, right?
In the flesh.
I'm here to talk.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I happen to be a lawyer.
For 30 minutes, I charge 5,000 yen to
consult, so either pay up or shut up. Huh?
I'm just kidding.
I wanted to see what it feels
like to be a cutthroat lawyer.
I see.
What's this guy doing?
You still have a hundred
points, don't you?
He's not a past sorcerer
who's been incarnated.
He's a modern sorcerer whose
technique was activated.
We can talk it out.
There's room for negotiation.
Okay, you've passed the
test with fine covers.
You've got more than enough, I can tell.
That's quite the Shikigami you have there.
I bet you're strong.
If you were weak, I'd just kill
you as another average mark.
But you're good.
Let's work together.
What gives?
I didn't agree to this.
What are you proposing?
How much do you actually know
so far about this culling game?
It's a ritual.
It uses the cursed energy
of the players inside the
barriers to ferry the people
of Japan to the other side.
And then changes them
into something inhuman.
Guess I should stay quiet about Tengen.
Really?
Do you know Kenjaku, then?
I knew there had to be at least one
sorcerer connected to Kenjaku in this game.
So, to be frank, we need your help.
We want to stop the culling game.
Timeout.
When I say stop the game, I
mean stop the obligated killing.
If we could use your hundred points, we'd
be able to add a new rule to the game.
Permit me to be frank as well.
I refuse.
Is that another joke? No.
I just sense huge potential in letting
the culling game continue as is.
Sometimes the law is powerless.
However, think about the
rules of this culling game.
If the power I've been granted is
real, then those rules must be too.
I think all your talk about players' cursed
energy being used inside the barriers?
It's probably just a bluff. A bluff?
Well, less of a bluff and more,
like you're describing Plan B or C.
Here's three reasons why.
The number of players, the strength gap
between players, and the barrier's rules.
If roughly 1,000 people were equally
split up between the 10 colonies,
that would come out to
100 people per colony.
However, among the players are
sources like Kashimo or Higuruma,
who are much stronger than the rest.
Those two alone have already
culled 60 sorcerers between them,
and I bet you there's a sorcerer just
like them in each of the other colonies.
So then the weak are weeded out early on.
Does that mean the culling
game ends as a stalemate?
He's confirmed my suspicions.
The colony's been too quiet.
It already has.
Well, at least it has here in Tokyo No. 1.
On top of that, there's the teleportation
when people enter the colonies.
It serves to spread out
players as they enter the game,
but its main goal is
likely to encourage an
early second awakening
of modern sorcerers.
There are some who die during
the teleportation, too.
Now, if he was really trying to
use the player's cursed energy,
then he would probably
want the greatest number of
sorcerers to fight for
the longest time possible.
What if people who broke
the rules were punished?
Not with the need of
indictments, prosecutions,
or arguments at trials, but
by pure physics instead.
Wouldn't that be wonderful?
I'll grant you there's issues
with the current rules,
but I want to watch over the system
serving as a basis for this game.
It'll ruin everything if it ends too soon.
I'd especially love to
witness at least once the
stripping of a technique
mentioned in Rules 2 and 8.
And it's better for the rules if
being stripped means death, too.
The Cullingame itself
is considered a ritual.
If we take too long, every
person in this nation will die.
That's not true.
The Cullingame insists on
its own ongoing longevity.
I don't really get that part either.
I'll rephrase it, then.
Let me use your 100 points, Higuruma!
Have you ever killed someone
who really ticked you off?
Feels better than I expected.
A hell of a lot better.
A Shikigami?
Higuruma has 100 points.
He might have killed 20 sorcerers already.
I can't just recklessly jump in.
I'll go on defense, but I'll be
ready to respond to any attack.
Domain expansion.
Deadly sentencing.
The idea of a rule not hindering
the continuation of the game,
it's just a cover for the real plan.
Mark my words,
when only the strong remain,
Kenjaku is going to drop a
bomb on this competition,
and the Cullingame will
fulfill its purpose.
Thank you.
Now, make your argument.
What if I'm judged guilty?
Judge man, please begin.
You mean I can lie?
You get one chance to make a statement.
I can't control cursed energy!
How can he hold his own against
me without cursed energy?
Hey, what a retrial!
One more time!